So you wanna go to war with me
You’re talking like you think you’re royalty
You think that I’m afraid
But I don’t break
I heard you question my stability
You think I’ll fall just like a guillotine
But I am here to stay
Won’t look away
A storm is coming
So you best start running
No you can’t control
Feel it in my bones
I’m coming for the coming for the I’m coming for the throne
I’m coming for the throne
So you wanna be my enemy
You should have known I’d never kiss the ring
Ice runs in my veins
Won’t play it safe
I don’t belong with your nobility
Who died and made you king of anything
You think that I’m insane
That’s your mistake
Kingdoms rise and fall I’ve come to take it all I’ll take it
I’ve come to take it
Kingdoms rise and fall I’ve come to take it all
I’ll take it all
A storm is coming
So you best start running
No you can’t control
Feel it in my bones
I’m coming for the coming for the I’m coming for the throne
I’m coming for the throne